你在干什么
What are you doing?
我重新整理了冰箱
I...reorganized the fridge.
看  最底下放肉跟奶制品
See, bottom shelf: meats and dairy.
中间放水果蔬菜
Middle shelf: fruits and vegetables.
最上面放过期食物
And top shelf: expired products.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
因为我无聊到快抓狂了
Because I am bored...Out of my mind.
我已经去过银行  邮局和干洗店了
I've already been to the bank, post office, and the dry cleaners.
老兄  你做完了我一周的事情
Dude, you just described seven days worth of stuff.
你要放轻松一点
You've got to spread it out a little, you know.
难道你从来没失业过吗
Haven't you ever been unemployed?
我不是失业  只是休假(有安息之意)
Hey, I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical!
少跟我传教
Hey, don't get religious on me, ok.
你现在的状况
A guy in your position
应该学会放轻松
needs to be a little better at relaxing. You know.
要不然我们家为什么会有安乐椅呢
Why do you think we have the comfortable chairs?
来  坐下
Huh...come here...sit down.
准备好没  看着
Ready? Watch.
干嘛  干坐着吗
So what, we just sit?
当然不  不会只是坐着  看好了
Ohh, no, no. We're not going to just sit. Watch.
喂  我是钱德勒·宾
Hello, Chandler Bing.
喂  宾先生  我爱你
Hello Mr. Bing...I love you.
够了  不管你是谁  别再打了
Alright, whoever this is, stop calling me!
你已经骚扰我半年了  一点也不好笑
It's been six months! It's not funny!
但我爱你呀
But I love you.
放过我吧  求你行行好  放过我吧
Leave me alone! For the love of God, leave me alone!!!
这只是周三的乐子
And that's Wednesday.
各位猜猜怎么着
Hey you guys, guess what?
英国人要打来啦
The British are coming?
你的笑话真冷
Ohh, you and your ways.
圣诞节快到了
Since it's Christmastime.
我要负责去收募捐款
I'm going to be one of those people collection donations.
我已经拿到了铃铛
Ohh. Yeah, I already have my bell
稍后就能拿到募捐桶
and later on...I get my bucket.
我要散播欢乐给大家
Yeah, yeah, I'm going to be out there spreading joy to the people.
去年散播的不够多
I mean, last year, I spread a little joy but not really enough.
今年一定要让全纽约都感受到
So this year, I'm going to do the whole city.
我有个高中同学也跟你一样
You know, I knew a girl in high school who did that.
她很受欢迎
She was very popular.
菲比  你要去哪里摇铃
So Pheebs, where are you doing all, your bell ringing?
我分到梅西百货旁的黄金地点
Ohh, they gave me a great spot. Right by Macys.
新人很少分到这么棒的地点
Yeah, they hardly ever give such a good spot to a rookie,
可是只有我会用二十五种语言说圣诞快乐
but I'm the only one who can sing "Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
我骗他们的
I lied.
我的天  丹尼在那边
Oh my god. Ok you guys, there's Danny. Watch.
你们看
Just watch this.
看见没  还在假装对我没兴趣
See?! Still pretending he's not interested.
他走过来了  大家装不认识他
Ohh, he's coming over. Just pretend like we don't know him.
完全不知道他是谁
We've forgotten who he is.
你们好
Hey guys.
你好  丹尼
Hey Danny.
是丹尼啊
Oh Danny！
丹尼  你认得瑞秋吧
Danny? You know Rachel?
她人很好  长得也不赖吧
She's nice. She's not bad to look at, right?
谢了  莫妮卡
Thanks, Mon.
当然
Well, of course.
你要不要跟她约会
Do you want to go out on a date with her?
-莫妮卡  -好啊  周五可以吗
- Monica!!! - Absolutely! Is Friday okay?
非常好  她等不及要赴约
Friday's perfect...She can't wait.
约会时我可以直接跟她说话吧
On the date, I will be able to talk to her directly?
周五见
See ya Friday.
你搞什么
Okay. What the hell was that?
算了  不用说了
You know what? Don't answer me.
我要跟丹尼约会了
I have a date with Danny.
我怎么会落选
How could I not get the part?
男主角就是二十九岁
The play was about a 29-year-old
出身皇后区的意大利演员
Italian actor from Queens.
泰莉雅·雪儿突然有空了
Well, Telia Shire suddenly became available.
她是女人啊
She's a woman!
我能说什么  她演得好极了
What can I say? She nailed it.
还有别的角色吗
Okay, is there anything else?
你一定又会拒绝
Well, you're just going to say no again but...
同志黄片
gay porn.
节日快乐  圣诞快乐
Happy Holidays. Feliz Navidad.
大家好  圣诞快乐
Allo, and Merry Christmas.
谢谢你  先生  给你快乐
Ohh thank you sir. Here's some joy.
怎么样了
I just wanted to see how it's going.
还可以
Well, it's going okay.
太好了  我也来捐款
Well good, here let me help you out.
谢谢
Oh, thanks!
新的麂皮外套吗  好像很贵的样子
Is that a new suede jacket? It looks really expensive.
是  不便宜
Yeah. I guess.
你刚做完指甲吗
Just get your nails done?
菲比  我只剩这些钱了  满意了吗
Yes Phoebe, but this is all I have. Okay?
谢啦  节日快乐  祝你幸福
Okay! Thanks! Happy Holidays, here's your joy.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  节日愉快
Thank you! And Happy Holidays.
等等  只能捐钱不能拿
Wait, you can't take the money out.
我跟你换零钱搭公车
I'm making change. I need change for the bus.
不能捐一块吗  这是为穷人募捐的
But, can't you leave the dollar? This money is for the poor.
我就是穷人  我要挤公车
I'm poor! I gotta take the bus!
好吧  节日快乐  不过...
Okay, Seasons Greetings and everything, but still...
关你屁事  小妞
Bite me, blondie!
我要给他点祝福外的东西  我要...
Oh, I'm going to give him something else besides joy, just...
那个角色根本就是为我而写的
That part was perfect for me!
我竟然落选了
I can't believe I didn't get it!
很遗憾
I'm sorry, man.
你知道该怎么做吗
Hey, y'know what you should do?
你要自己创造机会
You should make something happen for yourself.
例如写个剧本
Y'know, like-like write a play.
电影剧本
Write a movie! Huh?
就像写《心灵捕手》的那两个
I mean, what about those Good Will Hunting guys?
罗斯  少做白日梦了
Come on Ross be realistic, y'know?
就算我写出剧本
If I did write something,
哪有办法请到他们出演
what are the chances I could get those guys to star in it?
等等  我可以自己主演
Wait a second, I could star in it!
也可以
Or that.
我不会写剧本
I can't write!
我是说  我是演员
Y'know I mean I-I-I'm an actor,
没受过写作训练  我办不到
I don't have the discipline that takes, y'know? I can't do it.
我可以帮你
I'll help you.
我帮你制定出时间表  盯着你乖乖照做
Yeah, I'll make up a schedule and make sure you stick to it.
这样  我自己也有事做了
And plus, it'll give me something to do.
你真的愿意帮我吗
Really? You'd-you'd do that for me?!
-是啊  -谢谢
- Yeah! - Thanks!
开始慢慢来
All right, we'll start off slow.
今晚你只要想好
The only thing you have to do tonight
主角的名字
is come up with the name of your main character.
好了
Done!
不可以是乔伊
And it can't be Joey.
不是
It's not.
-乔瑟夫也不行  -这样啊
- Or Joseph. - Oh.
你怎么啦
Hey, what's up?
我刚看到丹尼跟女生搭地铁
I just saw Danny getting on the subway with a girl
他还搂着她
and he had his arm around her.
亲爱的  抱歉
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
你的确该抱歉  一切都要怪你
Well, you should be, this is all your fault!
你插手了我们的关系
You meddled in our relationship!!
你们根本就没关系
You had no relationship!!
不过我已经拟好计划
No, but I was doing my thing
一切都按部就班进行中
and everything was going according to the plan!
拜托  别再提你的计划
Oh God, stop with the plan!
你看到他跟别的女生在一起又如何
So what, so what you saw him with a girl?
有什么关系  他们不一定是情人
Who cares?! That doesn't mean anything!
你就快跟丹尼约会了
Now look, you're going to go out on a date with Danny
你可以迷得他
and you're going to be so charming
忘记地铁那个蠢妞
he's gonna forget all about that stupid subway girl.
那女生的确傻里傻气
She was kinda stupid.
你说得对  我要去约会
You're right. All right, I'm just gonna go on the date.
我会去赴约  这就是我的新计划
I'm gonna go on the date. That is the new plan.
快点
Come on, hurry!
"多疑"怎么写
Hey, how do you spell suspicious?
干嘛
Why?
我认为这个角色很"多疑"
Because I think this character is going to be suspicious about stuff.
太好了
Yes!
钱德勒·宾7分  钱德勒·宾0分
Chandler Bing, 7! Chandler Bing, 0.
看你玩真让我心烦
You're driving me crazy with that!
那我不玩了
Okay, I'll stop.
不用停  把碗放远点
Don't stop! Move the bowl further away!
这么近连罗斯都投得进
Ross could make that shot!
你水平很臭  不过至少在玩男人的游戏了
Well, you suck! But at least you suck at a man's game now.
想玩吗
You wanna play?
钱德勒  我不能玩游戏  罗斯就快回来了
Chandler, I can't be playing games, Ross is gonna be home soon.
我不写完五页
And I have to write five whole pages
就赶不上他的计划了
if I'm gonna stick to his schedule.
那先玩三十分钟
Well, so, play for the next 30 minutes
然后写到他回来
and then write until he gets home.
好
All right!
不过我建议  提高难度怎么样
But uh, listen, what do you say we crank it up a notch?
说得我心痒痒的
I'm intrigued.
好  我们需要点打火机油
All right, all we need is a little lighter fluid.
小心点
Okay, but be careful okay,
我还想要回租房安全押金呢
because I wanna get our security deposit back.
我们发明铁锤飞镖时  就拿不回来了
Yeah, I think we said good-bye to that when we invented hammer darts.
你还记得哪面墙壁是空心的吗
Do you even remember which part of the wall is not spackle?
就在这里
Uh yeah, right here.
谢谢  节日愉快
Thank you, Happy Holidays.
这是垃圾  小姐  你不能这样
Now, that's trash. Young lady, you can't...
拦住那位小姐  她竟然捐垃圾
Hey! Stop that young lady, she donated trash!
募捐桶着火了  救命
The charity's on fire! Help!
太好了  谢谢  我正需要
Oh good! Thank you, I need that.
搞什么鬼
Whoa! What is this?!
早上九点你就喝酒
It's nine o'clock in the morning!
我看看  场景房间
All right.  A room.
一名男子走进来  他看起来很多疑
A man enters, he looks suspicious.
就这样
That's it?
乔伊  你现在应该写完五页了
Joey, you're supposed to have five pages done by now!
还包括一个剧情高潮
Including an exciting incident!
这是什么
And what is, and what is all this?!
大火球游戏规则
The official rulebook of Fireball.
我们刚在玩这游戏
Yeah, that's the uh, game we were playing.
很好玩  道具就是一颗网球
Oh yeah, it's great! See you take a tennis ball,
一个碗  可燃液体
a bowl, and lighter fluid-Op! Op!
这对你的事业有帮助吗
This is helping your career?! Huh?
你不是想当演员吗
I thought you wanted to be an actor
而不是会引发官司的疯狂游戏的发明人
not the creator of crazy lawsuit game!
你说得对  我该工作了
You're right, you're right, I'll get back to work.
真为你害臊  你应该知道
And shame on you! You should know better,
乔伊要工作  快去写
Joey needs to work.  Now come on!
等你写完五页才还你
You can have this back when the five pages are done!
我今晚很开心
I had a really nice time tonight.
我也是  幸好莫妮卡约我们出来
So did I. I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
我很想请你进去  不过我妹来看我
I'd love to ask you in, but uh, my sister's visiting
她可能睡在沙发上
and I think she's asleep on the couch.
你妹妹  你妹妹睡在沙发上
You're sister? You're sister's asleep on the couch?
我上次看到你们搭地铁
Ohhh! I saw her with you on the subway
现在她睡在沙发上
and now she's asleep on the couch!
我就猜是你
Oh, I thought I heard you.
太好了  你起来了
Oh hey, great, you're up.
瑞秋  这是我妹妹克莉丝塔
Rachel, this is my sister Krista.
克莉丝塔  这位是瑞秋
Krista, this is Rachel.
-你好  -很高兴见到你
- Hi! - Nice to meet you.
你应该告诉我会来客人  我还没梳洗呢
I wish you'd told me we were having company, I'd fix myself up!
梳洗了就会好看点吗
Like it would help.
你真坏
You are so bad!
-你才坏  -你才坏
- You are! - You are!
你死定了  我跟你没完
You are so dead! I'm gonna get you.
见到你非常高兴
Uh, it was very nice meeting you.
没有人  没有人尊重我的募捐桶
Nobody! Nobody respects the bucket!
这些烂人什么都往里扔
You wouldn't believe what people put in here!
-你觉得这个看起来像是垃圾桶吗  -不
- Look! Okay, does this look like a garbage can to you? - No.
-像个烟灰缸吗  -不
- Does it look like an ashtray? - No.
像尿壶吗
Does it look like a urinal?
菲比  你还要回去继续吗
So Pheebs, are you gonna go back out there or what?
当然  不过我再也不会收废品了
Well, yeah! But I'm not gonna take anymore crap. Okay?
再也不当募捐好好小姐
No more Mrs. Nice Bucket!
好样的  你很厉害  你在街上混过
Yeah, good for you. Y'know you're tough, you lived on the streets.
我要做回街头菲比
Yeah, I'm gonna go back to being Street Phoebe.
不过  知道吗
Yeah! Oh but, y'know what?
也不能一模一样
I can't go totally back
街头菲比根本不会甩你们
because Street Phoebe really wouldn't be friends with you guys.
-可以问你们一个问题吗  -当然
- Hey, umm, can I ask you guys something? - Sure.
我没有兄弟  我不了解
Uh, I don't have any brothers so I don't know,
-你们会打来打去吗  -当然会
- but uh, did you guys wrestle? - Oh-oh, yeah.
经常的事  而且我从没输过
All the time. In fact, I was undefeated.
因为你以前重九十公斤
Uh, you weighted 200 pounds.
不过我还是跟猫一样矫捷
Still, I was quick as a cat.
我昨天碰到了丹尼的妹妹
Well, I met Danny's sister yesterday,
就是跟他一起搭地铁的那个
and uh that was actually the girl on the subway.
真的假的
Oh, you're kidding.
他们非常会  扭打
Yeah, they were very y'know...wrestley.
这样算正常吧
But, I guess that's normal?
我们现在不会这样了
We don't, we don't wrestle now.
自从我强过你就不打了
Yeah, not since I got too strong for you.
-强过我  -是的
- Too strong for me? - Yeah.
你现在要比划一下吗
You wanna go right now?
我可以立刻打败你  信不信
'Cause I'll take you right now, buddy! You wanna go?
没问题
Oh fine.
预备  开打
Ready? Wrestle!
知道吗
Okay, y'know what uh,
非常好  你们帮了大忙  多谢
actually, that's great. That helps a lot. Thanks.
兄弟们  赶快走
Guys, come on! Let's go!
冰球比赛再过二十分钟就开始了  快走  乔伊
The puck drops in 20 minutes! Come on, Joe!
乔伊不能去
Joey's not going.
我还没写完五页
I didn't finish my five pages.
明天再写不就成了
Well, why can't you do them tomorrow?
因为他明天要修改昨天的五页
Because tomorrow he's redoing yesterday's pages.
我昨天写的有待改进
Yesterday's pages did not reflect my best work.
别再逼他了  行吗
Why don't you cut him a little slack? Okay?
让他放松可能会写得更好
Maybe if he relaxes a little bit, he'll get some work done.
他已经够放松的了  这要感谢你和大火球
I think he's been relaxing enough, thanks to you and Fireball.
兄弟  如果你认为大火球很轻松
Dude, if you think Fireball's relaxing,
显然你没玩过
you've obviously have never played.
你这样对待乔伊
The only reason you're doing this to Joey
是因为你自己没事做
is because you're bored.
又不是乔伊害你失业的
Okay, it's not his fault that you're unemployed.
我不是失业  只是休假
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical!
你们别吵架
Come on look guys, don't fight.
我之所以这么做  是因为我是乔伊的朋友
And the reason I'm doing this is because I am Joey's friend.
如果你也是他朋友  就该学学我
And if you were a good friend, you'd be doing the same thing.
当朋友就得这么混帐吗
Oh, so being a good friend means acting like a total jerk?
要是真如你所说  你可真是我第一号好友
If it does? Then you're an amazing friend of mine.
别吵了
Hey-hey guys, hey!
大家玩场大火球友谊赛来解决吧
How about we settle this over a friendly game of Fireball? Huh?
我去拆掉烟雾报警器
I'll go unhook the smoke detectors!
现在来个了结
How about we settle this right now!
好了  谁也别想去看比赛
There! Now, no one's going to the game.
票是我花钱买的
I paid for those tickets!
不是  你总说会掏钱  可从没兑现过
No you didn't. You said you would, but you never did!
是的
Oh yeah!
我们终于爬到了山顶
...so we finally get to the top of the mountain
而这个笨蛋  居然忘了带相机
and airhead here forgets the camera!
我也做过这样的傻事
Oh, y'know the same thing happened to me one time.
什么时候的事
When did that happen to you?!
记得吗  我们在公园慢跑
Don't you remember when we were jogging in the park
碰到只可爱的小鸟  我想拍张照片
and we saw that really pretty bird and wanted to take a picture-
可竟然没带相机
I didn't have my camera!
首先  追油炸饼小贩可不是慢跑
First off all, chasing the Churo guy isn't jogging.
超好吃  你一定要吃一口
Oh, this is so good you have got to try it.
糟糕  裤子弄脏了
Oh, damn! I got it on my pants.
我来擦
Here, I'll get it.
最好上楼换条裤子  否则以后洗不掉
We'd better take these pants off upstairs or that stain's gonna set.
是的  今晚和你约会我打算穿这个
Yep. I'm gonna wear these on our date tonight.
真好
Oh, great!
再见了  我的天啊
Okay, bye!  Oh my God!!
难以置信
That was unbelievable!
瞧  我早说过了
Okay, see? I told you!
是啊  抱歉  瑞秋
Yeah, wow, sorry Rach.
我不相信他们是兄妹
I don't believe they're brother and sister.
他们是兄妹吗
They're brother and sister!!!
等一下  手张开给我检查
Wait a minute, open up your hand; let me take a look.
两毛五  一毛  线头
Quarter. Dime. Lint?
不要
Not interested in that.
这是什么  加拿大硬币
What's this? A Canadian coin?
走开
Get outta here!
不准在募捐桶旁边喝东西
No drinks near the bucket!
先放在那边后才准捐款
Set it down over there and then you can make a contribution!
少装一副可怜兮兮的样子
And you can leave the hurt bunny look over there too!
嗨  鲍伯  不是叫你走开了吗
Hi Bob! I thought I told you to get outta here!
菲比  我们接到投诉
Uh, Phoebe we've been getting complaints
我们会把你派到显略低调的地方
and uh, we're gonna move you to a less high-profile spot.
-什么  -以后这里由金洁负责
- What?! - Umm, Ginger's gonna take over this corner.
这个小妞没法混这里
That chick can't handle my corner.
你不走  我们就得赶你走
Look, either you leave, or we remove you.
好
Fine.
劝你一句  注意那个臭婆娘
All right, I'll give you one pointer. Look out for that bitch.
瑞秋  不是约七点吗
Oh, hey Rach! I thought we said seven?
知道吗  今天就算了吧
Yeah uh, y'know what uh, let's skip it.
什么  为什么
What?! Why?!
你们兄妹似乎...
Umm, you-you and your sister seem to have
非常要好
umm, a very special bond, and...
这下可好  又是这句话
Oh great! That special bond again!
我跟我妹感情好
Why do women have such a problem
为什么总让女人看不顺眼呢
with the fact that I'm close with my sister?
我不知道  听着
Well, okay, look. I don't know, listen,
我不知道具体情况  但是
I don't know what's going on here but let's...
你有兄弟吗
Do-do you, do you have brothers?
没  我有两个妹妹
No, I have two sisters.
其中一个很像男人婆
But one of them has a very masculine energy.
你们要好吗
Are you close with them?
不  她们不是什么好人
No-no, they're not very nice people.
听我说  我很喜欢你
Okay, listen, I really like you. Okay?
我觉得我们可以顺利交住下去
I think this can go somewhere.
我跟家人感情深厚
So what if I'm close to my family,
你就为了这点不理我吗
are you gonna let that stand in the way of us?
我也不知道
Well, uh, I-I don't know.
听你这么说也有道理
See when-when you put it that way y'know it does sort of...
丹尼  快点  洗澡水快凉了
Danny! Hurry up! The bath is getting cold!
-怎么了  -我先走了
- What? - Yeah, okay, I'll see you later.
街上有小孩在玩耍
There's some kids playing in the street,
你要不要去叫他们写作业  毁了他们的一天
you wanna go down there and give them a project, ruin their day?
如果他们手边有球  你就可以插上剃刀
Hey, if they have a ball maybe you can stick razor blades in it
教他们玩新游戏  "把球缝补好"
and teach them a new game, Gonna Need Stitches Ball.
兄弟们  我整个早上都待在图书馆
Hey guys! I was at the library all morning
-已经写完今天的五页了  -太好了
- and I already finished my five pages for today! - Yay!
好棒  我们可以去看昨晚的骑兵队比赛了
Great! Now, we can go to the Ranger game! Last night!
不行  门票被罗斯撕掉了
No dude, Ross tore up the tickets!
看来没有让你分心的事情
I guess when you don't have so many distractions,
就比较容易专心吧
it's easier for you to focus. Huh?
没人整天跟在你屁股后面说三道四
Yeah or also when you don't have somebody breathing down your neck
也比较得心应手吧
all the live long day!!
随你们说吧
Yeah, well, that's fine,
重要的是  我写完了
but the important thing is that I finished it.
而且写得还不错
And uh, I think it's really good, but
如果你们能对下台词  会很有帮助
y'know it'd really help me is if I could hear it.
可以帮忙吗
So would you guys read it for me?
-好  -好的
- Yeah. - All right.
一间普通的纽约公寓
Okay. "It's a typical New York City apartment.
两个男人正在家里  罗斯念吧
Two guys are hanging out." Ross
嗨  伙计
Hey man.
有什么事
What is up?
昨天是我错了  对不起
About yesterday, I was really wrong. I am sorry.
我才该道歉  对不起  我反应过头了
No, it was me. I'm sorry. I over reacted.
或许我们都有错  但我们都是为了朋友
Maybe it was both of us, but we had our best friend's interest...
我们都是为了朋友好
But we had our best friend's interest at heart.
我非常抱歉
Could I be more sorry.
我才是该道歉
I don't know,
我是愧疚的"物生古学家"
I'm one sorry polentologist.
好了  乔伊  我们懂了  对不起
All right Joey, we get it. I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
继续读下去  精彩的要上场了
Oh no! No-no, keep reading! The good part's coming up. Keep going.
对不起  钱德勒
I am sorry, Chandler.
对不起  罗斯
I am sorry, Ross.
帅哥上场
A handsome man enters.
你们好吗  我不知道你们在说什么
How's it going guys? I don't know what you two were talking about,
不过我要谢谢你们两个
but I'd like to say thanks to both of you.
你让我不放弃自己
You, you wouldn't let me give up on myself,
而你  与我一起创造了"大火球"
and you well you co-created Fireball.
剧终
The end.
这就花了你一整天吗
This took you all day?!
没有  我只写了五分钟
No-no, this only took five minutes.
其它时间都在写"终极大火球"游戏规则
I spent the rest of the day coming up with new, Ultimate Fireball.
场景是普通的纽约公寓
Okay, it's a typical New York City apartment.
屋内有两个女生
Two girls are just hanging out.
嗨  凯莉  你好吗
Hi, how are you doing Kelly?
我很好
I'm doing just fine!
老天  蒂芬妮  你今天好香
God, Tiffany, you smell so great!
我喷了新香水
It's my new perfume.
你过来一点才闻得仔细
Why don't you come closer where you can really appreciate it?
乔伊  你这个大变态
Oh, y'know Joey, you are sick!
真恶心
This is disgusting!
我才不读这些
I'm not reading this!
等等  帅哥马上要上场了
What?! Wait-wait-wait! The handsome man was about to enter!!